Guide to the Benjamin Sussman Papers, 1940-1995
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Benjamin Sussman papers 1940-1995
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Sussman, Benjamin
45.0 linear feet Extent: 33,750 Items
Benjamin Sussman (1921-2003) was an advertising executive and founder of the Sussman, Jordan and Pollacheck advertising agency. He also worked for Petersen Publishing and as a freelance writer. Accession (2009-0238) consists of Sussman's original library of clippings on a wide variety of subjects, including a large section of vintage publications, that he used as inspiration and information in his work. The clippings include advertisements as well as articles, and are sorted by subject or topic using Sussman's own filing system. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
RL.01270
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Benjamin Sussman Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2009.
Biographical Note
Benjamin Sussman was born in Connecticut and raised in Brooklyn, New York. He attended the Pratt Institute before joining the Marines and serving in the South Pacific during World War II.
Sussman began working in advertising in Los Angeles in the 1950s, where he worked for Thrifty Drug Store and Builders Emporium. He eventually opened Ben Sussman and Associates with his friend and partner, Jack Wallace. This later became Sussman, Jordan and Pollachek, and had accounts with companies like Kal Kan and Suzuki Motorcycles.
Outside of his own advertising agency, Sussman also wrote articles and columns for Petersen Publishing, particularly Motor Trend Magazine, and as a freelance writer for various advertising journals.
Collection Overview
Beginning in the 1940s, Sussman maintained an extensive library of clippings on a wide array of subjects, as well as a collection of vintage publications, which he drew upon in his research. This collection includes the majority of that library, as well as excerpts and clippings of Sussman's own writings. The collection includes advertisements as well as articles, and is sorted by subject or topic using Sussman's own filing system. Major themes include marketing, media, communications, production, design, merchandising and sales, publicity, industries and occupations, transportation, humans, animals, warfare, entertainment, holidays, and production sources.
Collection Arrangement
Materials have been kept in their original order and folders. Empty folders have been removed from the collection and are not listed in this finding aid. For access to Sussman's original inventory, please consult the Collection Control File.
Subject Headings
Sussman, Benjamin; Petersen Publishing Company; Communication in marketing; Advertising -- United States -- Sources; Los Angeles (Ca.); Clippings
Contents of Collection
- A: Marketing, (8 boxes)
  A-100 through A-131 are missing from the collection.
  - Reference binder for the collection (outdated) (Box 1)
  - Ben Sussman's work
    - Renault budget presentation (Box 1)
    - Cordial Medoc (Box 1)
    - Ogner/Mazda proposal (Box 1)
    - Toyo Kogyo/Rich Etc (Box 1)
    - Wanderlust (Box 1)
    - Import car dealer (Box 1)
    - Fitness center management (Box 1)
    - TLA (Box 1)
    - Avant Car (Box 1)
  - A-132: Agency Promotion, collateral (Box 1)
  - A-133: New Business, general (Box 1)
  - A-134: Advertising presentations (Box 1)
  - A-135: Proposals, agreements (Box 1)
  - A-135AF: Old proposals (Box 1)
  - A-136: Budgets, pre-1970 (Box 1)
  - A-137: Budgets, 1970-1973 (Box 1)
  - A-138: Budgets, 1974-1976 (Box 1)
  - A-139: Budgets, 1977-1980 (Box 1)
  - A-140: Budgets, 1981-1984 (Box 1)
  - A-141: Legal/government, general (Box 1)
  - A-142: Copyrights (Box 1)
  - A-143: Protecting ideas, concepts (Box 1)
  - A-144: Warranties (Box 1)
  - A-145: Fair trade (Box 1)
  - A-146: Product recalls (Box 1)
  - A-147: Product endorsements (Box 1)
  - A-148: FTO, FTC (Box 1)
  - A-150: Consumerism (Box 1)
  - A-151: Agency liability (Box 1)
  - A-152: Legislative participation (Box 1)
  - A-153: Ethics, general (Box 2)
  - A-155: Industry self-regulation (Box 2)
  - A-156: Clients, general (Box 2)
  - A-157: Retail clients (Box 2)
  - A-158: Industrial clients (Box 2)
  - A-159: Advertising managers (Box 2)
  - A-160: PR managers (Box 2)
  - A-161: Brand managers (Box 2)
  - A-162: Marketing managerse (Box 2)
  - A-163: Sales managers (Box 2)
  - A-164: Marketing, general (Box 2)
  - A-165: The Marketing Plan (Box 2)
  - A-166: Promotional objectives (Box 2)
  - A-167: Small business (Box 2)
  - A-168: Distribution, general (Box 2)
  - A-169: Private labels, brands (Box 2)
  - A-170: Co-op advertising (Box 2)
  - A-171: Associations, general (Box 2)
  - A-200: New products, general (Box 2)
  - A-201: Diversification/growth (Box 2)
  - A-202: New product research (Box 2)
  - A-203: New product development (Box 2)
  - A-204: New product introductions (Box 2)
  - A-205: Test marketing (Box 2)
  - A-206: Sampling (Box 3)
  - A-300: Research, general (Box 3)
  - A-301: Research effectiveness (Box 3)
  - A-302: Attitudes, opinions (Box 3)
  - A-303: Research personalities (Box 3)
  - A-304: Research associations (Box 3)
  - A-305: Research sources, general (Box 3)
  - A-306: Research companies, miscellaneous (Box 3)
  - A-307: A.C. Nielson (Box 3)
  - A-308: Dun & Bradstreet (Box 3)
  - A-309: ARB (Box 3)
  - A-310: Techniques, miscellaneous (Box 3)
  - A-311: Market share measurement (Box 3)
  - A-312: Motivational research (Box 3)
  - A-313: Psychographics (Box 3)
  - A-314: Surveys, commentary (Box 3)
  - A-315: Surveys, methodology (Box 3)
  - A-316: Print audits, general (Box 3)
  - A-317: Polity (Box 3)
  - A-318: Simmons (Box 3)
  - A-319: Starch (Box 3)
  - A-320: BRI (Box 3)
  - A-321: Broadcast audits, general (Box 3)
  - A-322: Radio audits (Box 3)
  - A-323: Television audits (Box 3)
  - A-400: Demographics, general (Box 3)
  - A-401: Neighborhoods (Box 3)
  - A-402: Geography (Box 3)
  - A-403: Population (Box 3)
  - A-404: Social index (Box 3)
  - A-405: Sex (Box 3)
  - A-406: Income, buying power (Box 3)
  - A-407: Age, general (Box 3)
  - A-408: Youth market (Box 4)
  - A-409: Senior citizens (Box 4)
  - A-410: Female markets (Box 4)
  - A-411: Advertising to women (Box 4)
  - A-412: Females, general (Box 4)
  - A-413: Female employment (Box 4)
  - A-414: Feminism, pre-1920 (Box 4)
  - A-415: Feminism, post-1920 (Box 4)
  - A-500: Social markets, general (Box 4)
  - A-501: Ethnic markets, general (Box 4)
  - A-502: EEOC (Box 4)
  - A-503: Immigrants, general (Box 4)
  - A-504: American Indians, general (Box 4)
  - A-505: Indians, pre-1900 (Box 4)
  - A-506: Indians, post-1900 (Box 4)
  - A-507: Chinese-Americans (Box 4)
  - A-508: Italian-Americans (Box 4)
  - A-509: Japanese-Americans (Box 4)
  - A-510: Jews, pre-1914 (Box 4)
  - A-511: Jews, post-1914 (Box 4)
  - A-512: Jewish personalities (Box 4)
  - A-513: Negro markets (Box 4)
  - A-514: Black history (Box 4)
  - A-515: Black personalities (Box 4)
  - A-516: Scandinavian-Americans (Box 4)
  - A-517: Scotch/Irish-Americans (Box 4)
  - A-518: Spanish surname markets (Box 4)
  - A-519: Mexican-American history (Box 4)
  - A-600: U.S. Markets, general (Box 4)
  - A-601: National parks/monuments (Box 4)
  - A-602: American cities, general (Box 4)
  - A-603: New England (Box 4)
  - A-604: North Central area (Box 4)
  - A-605: The South (Box 4)
  - A-606: Midwest (Box 4)
  - A-607: Sunbelt (Box 4)
  - A-608: The Southwest (Box 4)
  - A-609: Pacific Northwest (Box 4)
  - A-610: East vs. West (Box 4)
  - A-611: State vs. State (Box 4)
  - A-620: California, historical (Box 4)
  - A-621: California parks and monuments (Box 4)
  - A-622: Northern California, general (Box 4)
  - A-623: Northern California, historical (Box 4)
  - A-624: Sacramento (Box 4)
  - A-625: San Francisco/Bay Area (Box 4)
  - A-626: Fresno (Box 4)
  - A-627: Monterey (Box 4)
  - A-628: San Jose (Box 4)
  - A-629: Imperial Valley (Box 4)
  - A-630: California deserts (Box 4)
  - A-631: Southern California, general (Box 4)
  - A-632: Southern California, historical (Box 4)
  - A-633: Los Angeles, general (Box 4)
  - A-634: S.F. Valley (Box 4)
  - A-635: Downtown (Box 4)
  - A-636: East L.A. (Box 4)
  - A-637: Hollywood (Box 4)
  - A-638: Westwood (Box 4)
  - A-639: Santa Monica (Box 4)
  - A-640: Malibu (Box 4)
  - A-641: Pasadena (Box 4)
  - A-642: San Bernardino (Box 4)
  - A-643: Santa Barbara (Box 4)
  - A-644: Solvang (Box 4)
  - A-645: Catalina (Box 4)
  - A-646: San Gabriel/Pomona Valley (Box 4)
  - A-647: Coast Cities, general (Box 4)
  - A-648: Long Beach (Box 4)
  - A-649: Orange County, general (Box 5)
  - A-650: Irvine/Newport (Box 5)
  - A-651: San Diego (Box 5)
  - A-701: Alabama (Box 5)
  - A-702: Alaska (Box 5)
  - A-703: Arizona (Box 5)
  - A-704: Arkansas (Box 5)
  - A-705: California, general (Box 5)
  - A-706: Colorado (Box 5)
  - A-707: Connecticut (Box 5)
  - A-708: Delaware (Box 5)
  - A-709: Florida (Box 5)
  - A-710: Georgia (Box 5)
  - A-711: Hawaii (Box 5)
  - A-712: Idaho (Box 5)
  - A-713: Illinois (Box 5)
  - A-714: Indiana (Box 5)
  - A-716: Kansas (Box 5)
  - A-717: Kentucky (Box 5)
  - A-718: Louisiana (Box 5)
  - A-719: Maine (Box 5)
  - A-720: Maryland (Box 5)
  - A-721: Massachusetts (Box 5)
  - A-722: Michigan (Box 5)
  - A-724: Mississippi (Box 5)
  - A-725: Missouri (Box 5)
  - A-726: Montana (Box 5)
  - A-727: Nebraska (Box 5)
  - A-728: New Hampshire (Box 5)
  - A-729: New Jersey (Box 5)
  - A-730: New Mexico (Box 5)
  - A-731: New York (Box 5)
  - A-732: Nevada (Box 5)
  - A-733: North Carolina (Box 5)
  - A-735: Ohio (Box 5)
  - A-736: Oklahoma (Box 5)
  - A-737: Oregon (Box 5)
  - A-738: Pennsylvania (Box 5)
  - A-739: Rhode Island (Box 5)
  - A-740: South Carolina (Box 5)
  - A-742: Tennessee (Box 5)
  - A-743: Texas (Box 5)
  - A-744: Utah (Box 5)
  - A-745: Vermont (Box 5)
  - A-746: Virginia (Box 5)
  - A-747: Washington (Box 5)
  - A-748: Washington, D.C. (Box 5)
  - A-749: West Virginia (Box 5)
  - A-751: Wyoming (Box 5)
  - A-800: International markets, general (Box 5)
  - A-801: Multinationals (Box 5)
  - A-802: Exporting (Box 5)
  - A-803: Importing (Box 5)
  - A-804: International advertising (Box 5)
  - A-805: International marketing, general (Box 6)
  - A-806: Expatriates/assignments (Box 6)
  - A-807: Algeria (Box 6)
  - A-808: Angola (Box 6)
  - A-810: Australia (Box 6)
  - A-811: Austria (Box 6)
  - A-812: Bahamas (Box 6)
  - A-813: Belgium (Box 6)
  - A-814: Bolivia (Box 6)
  - A-815: Brazil (Box 6)
  - A-816: Bulgaria (Box 6)
  - A-817: Burma (Box 6)
  - A-818: Burundi (Box 6)
  - A-819: Cambodia (Box 6)
  - A-820: Canada (Box 6)
  - A-821: Chad (Box 6)
  - A-822: Chile (Box 6)
  - A-823: China (Box 6)
  - A-824: Colombia (Box 6)
  - A-825: Congo (Box 6)
  - A-826: Crete (Box 6)
  - A-827: Cuba (Box 6)
  - A-828: Cypress (Box 6)
  - A-829: Czechoslovakia (Box 6)
  - A-830: Denmark (Box 6)
  - A-831: Dominican Republic (Box 6)
  - A-832: Ecuador (Box 6)
  - A-833: Egypt (Box 6)
  - A-834: Ethiopia (Box 6)
  - A-835: Fiji (Box 6)
  - A-836: Finland (Box 6)
  - A-837: France (Box 6)
  - A-838: Germany, West (Box 6)
  - A-839: Germany, East (Box 6)
  - A-840: Germany, general (Box 6)
  - A-841: Ghana (Box 6)
  - A-842: Great Britain (Box 6)
  - A-843: Greece (Box 6)
  - A-844: Guatemala (Box 6)
  - A-845: Haiti (Box 6)
  - A-846: Hong Kong (Box 6)
  - A-847: Hungary (Box 6)
  - A-848: Indonesia (Box 6)
  - A-849: Iceland (Box 6)
  - A-850: India/Pakistan/Bangladesh (Box 6)
  - A-851: India (Box 6)
  - A-852: Iran (Box 6)
  - A-853: Iraq (Box 6)
  - A-854: Ireland, general (Box 6)
  - A-855: Ireland, Northern (Box 6)
  - A-856: Ivory Coast (Box 6)
  - A-857: Israel (Box 6)
  - A-858: Italy (Box 6)
  - A-859: Japan (Box 7)
  - A-860: Jordan (Box 7)
  - A-861: Kenya (Box 7)
  - A-862: Korea (Box 7)
  - A-863: Laos (Box 7)
  - A-864: Lebanon (Box 7)
  - A-865: Libya (Box 7)
  - A-866: Luxembourg (Box 7)
  - A-867: Malasia (Box 7)
  - A-868: Malta (Box 7)
  - A-869: Mexico (Box 7)
  - A-870: Monaco (Box 7)
  - A-871: Morocco (Box 7)
  - A-872: Netherlands (Box 7)
  - A-873: New Zealand (Box 7)
  - A-874: Nicaragua (Box 7)
  - A-875: Nigeria (Box 7)
  - A-876: Norway (Box 7)
  - A-877: Panama (Box 7)
  - A-878: Peru (Box 7)
  - A-879: Phillipines (Box 7)
  - A-880: Poland (Box 7)
  - A-881: Portugal (Box 7)
  - A-882: Puerto Rico (Box 7)
  - A-883: Rhodesia (Box 7)
  - A-884: Romania (Box 7)
  - A-885: Russia, Czarist (Box 7)
  - A-886: Russia, Soviet (Box 7)
  - A-887: Samoa (Box 7)
  - A-888: Scotland (Box 7)
  - A-889: Singapore (Box 7)
  - A-890: Solomon Islands (Box 7)
  - A-891: South Africa, A and B (Box 7)
  - A-892: Spain (Box 7)
  - A-893: Sweden (Box 7)
  - A-894: Switzerland (Box 7)
  - A-895: Syria (Box 7)
  - A-896: Tanzania (Box 7)
  - A-897: Thailand (Box 7)
  - A-898: Tunisia (Box 7)
  - A-899: Turkey (Box 7)
  - A-900: Uganda (Box 7)
  - A-901: Uruguay (Box 7)
  - A-905: Asia, general (Box 8)
  - A-906: South America, general (Box 8)
  - A-907: Caribbean, general (Box 8)
  - A-908: Europe, general (Box 8)
  - A-909: Scandinavia, general (Box 8)
  - A-910: Middle East, general (Box 8)
  - A-911: Africa, general (Box 8)
  - A-912: South Seas, Pacific, general (Box 8)
  - A-913: United Nations (Box 8)
  - A-914: League of Nations (Box 8)
  - A-915: Common Market (Box 8)
- B: Media, (2 boxes)
  - B-100: Media, general (Box 8)
  - B-101: Media strategy/mix (Box 8)
  - B-102: Buying, general (Box 8)
  - B-103: Media buying services (Box 8)
  - B-104: Media's promotion (Box 8)
  - B-105: Print, general (Box 8)
  - B-106: Print audits, general (Box 8)
  - B-107: Broadcasts, general (Box 8)
  - B-108: Broadcast monitoring (Box 8)
  - B-200: Newspapers, general (Box 8)
  - B-201: Newspapers, creative (Box 8)
  - B-202: Inserts, spectaculars (Box 8)
  - B-203: Supplements, comics (Box 8)
  - B-204: Newspaper reports through 1975 (Box 8)
  - B-205: Newspaper reports from 1976 (Box 8)
  - B-206: Newspaper advertising bureau (Box 8)
  - B-207: Associations, general (Box 8)
  - B-208: Classified advertising (Box 8)
  - B-209: Rate structures (Box 8)
  - B-210: California newspapers (Box 8)
  - B-211: Suburban press (Box 8)
  - B-212: Ethnic newspapers (Box 8)
  - B-213: Underground newspapers (Box 8)
  - B-300: Magazines, general (Box 8)
  - B-301: Magazines, creative (Box 8)
  - B-302: Magazine reports through 1975 (Box 8)
  - B-303: Magazine reports from 1976 (Box 8)
  - B-304: Magazine publishers association (Box 8)
  - B-305: Magazine associations, general (Box 8)
  - B-306: Reps/groups (Box 8)
  - B-307: Magazine buying criteria (Box 8)
  - B-308: Consumer magazines (Box 8)
  - B-309: Farm magazines (Box 8)
  - B-310: Minority/ethnic magazines (Box 8)
  - B-311: Regional editions (Box 8)
  - B-312: City/regional editions (Box 8)
  - B-313: Programs/entertainment (Box 8)
  - B-400: Business magazines, general (Box 8)
  - B-401: Creative (Box 8)
  - B-402: Industrial advertising strategy (Box 8)
  - B-403: Reports through 1975 (Box 8)
  - B-404: Reports from 1976 (Box 8)
  - B-409: Religious/fraternal (Box 8)
  - B-500: Radio, general (Box 9)
  - B-501: Radio, creative (Box 9)
  - B-502: Commercial production (Box 9)
  - B-503: Broadcasters associations (Box 9)
  - B-504: Reps/groups (Box 9)
  - B-505: AM vs. FM (Box 9)
  - B-506: Programming, general (Box 9)
  - B-507: Western radio through 1975 (Box 9)
  - B-508: Western radio from 1976 (Box 9)
  - B-509: Spot radio (Box 9)
  - B-510: Network radio (Box 9)
  - B-511: Industrial radio (Box 9)
  - B-512: Underground stations (Box 9)
  - B-513: Ratings/measurements (Box 9)
  - B-600: Television, general (Box 9)
  - B-601: Network TV, general (Box 9)
  - B-602: Spot TV, general (Box 9)
  - B-603: UHF, general (Box 9)
  - B-604: Independent TV (Box 9)
  - B-605: Cable TV advertising (Box 9)
  - B-606: FCC (Box 9)
  - B-607: TV bureau of advertising (Box 9)
  - B-608: Broadcasters associations, general (Box 9)
  - B-609: Show sponsorship (Box 9)
  - B-610: Programming, packaging (Box 9)
  - B-611: Plugs, game shows, barter (Box 9)
  - B-612: Audience/viewing (Box 9)
  - B-613: Ratings (Box 9)
  - B-614: Commercials, general (Box 9)
  - B-615: TV commercial production (Box 9)
  - B-616: Production companies (Box 9)
  - B-617: Film vs. tape (Box 9)
  - B-618: Talent, casting (Box 9)
  - B-619: Costs/budgets (Box 9)
  - B-700: Outdoor, general (Box 9)
  - B-702: Outdoor effectiveness (Box 9)
  - B-703: Legal, controversial (Box 9)
  - B-704: Outdoor associations (Box 9)
  - B-705: Outdoor operators (Box 9)
  - B-706: Circulation, audits (Box 9)
  - B-707: Creative, specs (Box 9)
  - B-708: Industrial outdoor (Box 9)
  - B-709: Foreign outdoor (Box 9)
  - B-800: Transit advertising, general (Box 9)
  - B-802: Creative, production (Box 9)
  - B-900: Miscellaneous media (Box 9)
  - B-901: Yellow pages (Box 9)
  - B-902: Closed circuit TV (Box 9)
  - B-903: Theater advertising (Box 9)
  - B-907: Taxis, trucks (Box 9)
  - B-908: Telephone advertising (Box 9)
  - B-910: Campus media (Box 9)
  - B-911: Foreign, international media (Box 9)
- C: Communications, (2 boxes)
  - C-101: Themes/slogans (Box 9)
  - C-102: Copy styles, general (Box 9)
  - C-103: Fashion copy (Box 9)
  - C-104: Long/short copy (Box 9)
  - C-105: Controversy; ad copy (Box 9)
  - C-106: Sussman rejects (Box 9)
  - C-201: Stream of consciousness (Box 9)
  - C-202: Origins (Box 9)
  - C-203: Historical (Box 9)
  - C-204: Nostalgia (Box 9)
  - C-205: Esperanto (Box 9)
  - C-300: Semantics (Box 9)
  - C-301: Euphemisms (Box 9)
  - C-400: Editorial copy, general (Box 9)
  - C-401: Style guides (Box 9)
  - C-500: Personal communications (Box 9)
  - C-501: Corporate communications (Box 9)
  - C-502: Bureaucracy/legalese (Box 9)
  - C-600: Humor, general (Box 9)
  - C-601: Humor in editorial, general (Box 9)
  - C-602: Humor in advertising, general (Box 9)
  - C-603: Humorous copy (Box 9)
  - C-604: Humor, historical (Box 9)
  - C-605: Ethnic humor (Box 9)
  - C-606: Daffy definitions (Box 9)
  - C-607: Malapropisms (Box 9)
  - C-608: Limericks (Box 9)
  - C-609: Puns (Box 9)
  - C-610: Jokes (Box 9)
  - C-611: Cartoons (Box 10)
  - C-700: Maxims/quotes (Box 10)
  - C-701: Social commentary, general (Box 10)
  - C-702: Free enterprise system (Box 10)
  - C-703: Welfarism/socialism (Box 10)
  - C-704: Political commentary (Box 10)
  - C-800: Speechmaking, general (Box 10)
  - C-801: Speeches, scripts (Box 10)
  - C-900: TV commercial dialogue scripts (Box 10)
  - C-901: TV commercial copy commentary (Box 10)
  - C-902: Radio commercial copy scripts (Box 10)
  - C-903: Radio copy scripts (Box 10)
  - C-904: Broadcast scripts, general (Box 10)
- D: Collateral/Production, (2 boxes)
  - D-100: Collateral material, general (Box 10)
  - D-101: Production, general (Box 10)
  - D-102: Associations, clubs (Box 10)
  - D-103: Historical processes (Box 10)
  - D-104: Printing processes, general (Box 10)
  - D-105: Letterpress (Box 10)
  - D-106: Offset, lithography (Box 10)
  - D-107: Rotogravure (Box 10)
  - D-108: 3-D printing (Box 10)
  - D-109: Silk screen (Box 10)
  - D-110: Captive plants (Box 10)
  - D-111: Paper stock, general (Box 10)
  - D-200: Stationary, general (Box 10)
  - D-201: Letterheads, general (Box 10)
  - D-202: Letterheads, embossed (Box 10)
  - D-203: Watermarks (Box 10)
  - D-204: Memos/social stationary (Box 10)
  - D-205: Business cards (Box 10)
  - D-206: Envelopes, general (Box 10)
  - D-207: Envelopes, 1st class (Box 10)
  - D-208: Envelopes, bulk rate (Box 10)
  - D-209: Reply envelopes (Box 10)
  - D-210: Business reply cards (Box 10)
  - D-300: Business forms, general (Box 10)
  - D-301: Expense forms (Box 10)
  - D-302: Billing forms (Box 10)
  - D-303: Purchase orders (Box 10)
  - D-304: Media forms (Box 10)
  - D-305: Production forms (Box 10)
  - D-306: Model, talent forms (Box 10)
  - D-307: News release forms (Box 10)
  - D-308: Editorial forms (Box 10)
  - D-309: Sussman graphics (Box 10)
  - D-400: Direct marketing, general (Box 10)
  - D-401: Direct mail advertising (Box 11)
  - D-402: Sales letters, general (Box 11)
  - D-403: Subscription mailers (Box 11)
  - D-404: Real estate mailers (Box 11)
  - D-405: Mail order, general (Box 11)
  - D-406: Mailing lists (Box 11)
  - D-407: Postal regulations (Box 11)
  - D-408: U.S. Postal Service (Box 11)
  - D-409: Private mail delivery (Box 11)
  - D-410: Invitations (Box 11)
  - D-411: Moving announcements (Box 11)
  - D-412: Birth announcements (Box 11)
  - D-500: House Organs, general (Box 11)
  - D-501: Annual Reports (Box 11)
  - D-502: Corporate booklets (Box 11)
  - D-503: Employee manuals (Box 11)
  - D-504: Internation publications (Box 11)
  - D-505: Customer magazines (Box 11)
  - D-506: Newsletters (Box 11)
  - D-507: Catalogs (Box 11)
  - D-600: Merchandising, general (Box 11)
  - D-601: Slide rules, charts (Box 11)
  - D-602: Posters (Box 11)
  - D-603: Menus (Box 11)
  - D-604: Ex libris (Box 11)
  - D-605: Coupons, certificates (Box 11)
  - D-606: Money (Box 11)
  - D-607: Labels, tags (Box 11)
  - D-608: Emblems (Box 11)
  - D-609: Buttons (Box 11)
  - D-610: Name tags (Box 11)
  - D-611: Balloons (Box 11)
  - D-612: Flags, mobiles (Box 11)
  - D-613: POP, historic (Box 11)
  - D-614: POP, general (Box 11)
  - D-615: Pre-packs (Box 11)
  - D-616: Window display (Box 11)
  - D-617: Signs, general (Box 11)
  - D-700: Awards, general (Box 11)
- E: Design, (2 boxes)
  - E-100: Trademarks, general (Box 12)
  - E-101: Trademark updating (Box 12)
  - E-102: Corporate identity programs (Box 12)
  - E-200: Borders, ornaments (Box 12)
  - E-300: Coat-of-arms, heraldry (Box 12)
  - E-301: Coat-of-arms, nations (Box 12)
  - E-302: Coat-of-arms, states (Box 12)
  - E-303: Coat-of-arms, commercial (Box 12)
  - E-400: U.S.A. symbols, general (Box 12)
  - E-401: American eagle (Box 12)
  - E-402: Uncle Sam (Box 12)
  - E-500: Maps, general (Box 12)
  - E-501: Maps, U.S., dated (Box 12)
  - E-502: Maps, dated, general (Box 12)
  - E-503: Maps, marketing (Box 12)
  - E-600: Nostalgia, general (Box 12)
  - E-601: Woodcuts, public domain (Box 12)
  - E-602: Antique equipment (Box 12)
  - E-700: Hand lettering, general (Box 12)
  - E-701: Antique styles (Box 12)
  - E-702: Scripts (Box 12)
  - E-703: Avant garde (Box 12)
  - E-704: Effects, miscellaneous (Box 12)
  - E-800: Layout, general-A (Box 12)
  - E-800: Layout, general-B (Box 12)
  - E-800: Layout, general-C (Box 12)
  - E-801: Collateral material (Box 12)
  - E-802: Rebus (Box 12)
  - E-803: Scatter-plan (Box 12)
  - E-804: Shadow box (Box 12)
  - E-805: Collage (Box 12)
  - E-806: Created/altered objects (Box 12)
  - E-807: Body paint: objects (Box 12)
  - E-808: Body paint: humans (Box 12)
  - E-900: Sex in advertising, general (Box 12)
  - E-901: Commentary/legal (Box 12)
  - E-902: Double entendres (Box 12)
  - E-903: Graphics, general (Box 12)
  - Sensitive products (Box 13)
  - E-905: Out-of-date (Box 13)
  - E-906: Television (Box 13)
  - E-908: Merchandising (Box 13)
  - E-909: Editorial/publicity (Box 13)
  - E-1000: Packaging, general (Box 13)
  - E-1001: Packaging, legal (Box 13)
  - E-1002: Packaging design (Box 13)
  - E-1100: Art forms, general (Box 13)
  - E-1101: Op, pop, etc. (Box 13)
  - E-1102: Portraiture (Box 13)